The second one I have kept in red is ICC
Pro's numbers, they were bought during the market,
although those too were weak, they were good
numbers and I am keeping ICC Lombard in red, the
headline numbers will
look good, general insurance of such people will be
seen near this number and that is why
I thought of mentioning it in red today,
due to higher provisioning, the
estimate missed a little, the
management is good, there are a
lot of issues in the internals
regarding the new business premium, the
headline numbers are okay, the internals are
weak, hence I have kept ICC Lombard in red for today, but it
enjoys very good moves, it is
fond of good petgiri,
for the reaction of the number in its place, the
result
update came yesterday